mobilesyrup.net 2016-05-30

# Privacy Policy | MobileSyrup.com

### Privacy Policy

MobileSyrup.com, (“We”, “Us”, “Our” etc.) believes that your personal information deserves protection and We subscribe to the privacy principles set out in the Government of Canada’s Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. This privacy policy describes Our practices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your personal information. By using Our websites you consent and agree to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information and to the privacy practices set out in this policy. We expressly reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time with or without notice to you.

 **How do we collect and use personal information?**  
We are in the business of providing a forum for the useful exchange of information about products and services between Our users. As part of providing these services, We collect personal information from Our users in a number of ways.

 **Submissions and Emails**  
When you submit a deal or rebate through Our on-line form or via email, We will not post your email but will post the name you have provided with the submission. If you do not wish your name to be posted, you can indicate it in your submission or ask Us to remove your name from the posting. We may enter you into contests from time to time and would use your email to notify you if you are a winner.

 **Comments**  
In order to post a comment on Our websites, you must be a registered user. When you post a comment on Our websites, your comment and user name will be accessible for viewing by all users of Our websites.

 **Contests**  
From time to time, We may run contests for Our users, in which case We would use your email or private messages to notify you if you are a winner. We may also run contests or promotions on Our websites that you can enter by filling an entry form. If you enter a contest, We will use your email address or other contact information to notify you if you are a winner. You may also have the option of providing additional information that is not related to awarding prizes for the contest. This information serves as a survey of Our users and enables Us to improve Our websites to better meet your preferences and to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. In Our entry forms, if you do not want Us to use your personal information for such purposes, you can either not participate in the contest or provide only the minimum information necessary to participate in the contest.

 **Forums**  
In order to participate in Our on-line forums, you need to create a user account by submitting a user name, email address and password. We will display your user name with your postings on the forum. You may also choose to have Us display your email with your postings so that other users can contact you.

 **Polls**  
We may from time to time poll Our users on various matters of interest. If you vote in one of Our polls, We will record your answer to report to you which polls you have voted for and also to avoid allowing multiple votes by one person. Some polls may make your vote publicly available by displaying your user name alongside your vote to other users of Our websites. We indicate in advance what poll results are “private” and what poll results are “publicly available”.

 **Testimonials**  
We may wish, from time to time, to post your comments or submissions as sample testimonials from Our users, in which case We will ask for your permission in advance.

 **Statistics**  
We may also use personal information and data collected through your emails and use of Our websites and the Surveys Website to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use and for sharing with Our affiliates, service providers, suppliers, merchants, partners, sponsors, licensors, advertisers or other third parties with whom we have business relationships (hereinafter individually “Third Party” or collectively “Third Parties”). These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any information that could identify you personally.

 **How do We protect your personal information?**  
We collect your personal information onto servers hosted by a reputable third party website hosting company and are restricted access servers. If you wish to obtain further information about Our hosting company and its security measures, please email Our Privacy Officer at info@mobilesyrup.com.

If all or part of any of Our websites or Our company is acquired or otherwise transferred to another entity, any personal information you have provided to Us may be transferred as part of that transaction. However, we will take steps to assure that such personal information, if any, is used in a manner consistent with the privacy policy under which it was collected.

 **What other organizations collect information?**  
The online advertisements you see on Our website are provided by various advertising agencies or Google. These third-party advertising companies may use non-personal information about your visits to Our websites in order to serve ads about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like to know more about what information is collected, how Our third party advertising companies use that information, and your choices about not having that information used by these companies, please click here for [Google](http://www.google.com/). You should know that Google uses cookies to serve ads on Our websites. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads about goods and services of interest to you based on your visit to Our websites and/or other sites on the Internet. For more information about the DART cookie you should visit <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx>. You may also opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

From time to time, We run promotions and contests that may be operated or administered by third party service providers on Our behalf, in which case personal information may be collected and stored by such third party, or disclosed to such third party by Us, for the purpose of the contest. If you have opted to receive marketing materials from third parties or Us through your use of Our websites, the information you provide may be used to send you such marketing materials.

 **Exceptions**  
We reserve the right to use and disclose personal information to comply with applicable laws and regulations and local, provincial and national governmental requests, to operate Our websites properly, or to protect Our rights and property and those of Our users or Third Parties.

 **Contact Information**  
For questions or concerns regarding your personal information and Our privacy policy, or to update, correct or delete your personal information, please contact:

Privacy Officer  
MobileSyrup.com  
Toronto, ON  
info@mobilesyrup.com

Last Revised February 17, 2011

Read more: [http://www.mobilesyrup.com](http://www.mobilesyrup.com/)
